

## ROMERO LUCAS DANIEL



ROMEROLUCASDANIEL@OUTLOOK.COM

**ADDRESS:** 

DON TORCUATO - TIGRE



PHONE: +54 01159479544



WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/ROMEROLU CASDANIEL

#### **OBJECTIVES**

I want to keep learning and improving as a professional, get a better experience and be a good reference.

I really enjoy learning new technologies and being self-taught.

I like the good atmosphere with a committed team.

My first goal is to never stop learning.



https://github.com/LucasRomero

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Full Stack Web Developer Net Core, Angular Tips Salud

#### June 2021 - Present.

- I'm working on big project the main that medical professionals can keep track of their patients, and other functionalities. My tasks are create new features and fix bugs. I work with Angular 2 and 4, with .Net core, in this company has a particular framework for the API in .Net Core and .Net developed by them and I use that for projects and modules. We use many modules. We use microservices to improve the response of each service.
- Sql Server 2012. Scrum Methodology. Task management with Team Server Fundation (TFS). Git Hub.
- The project uses: SignalR, DataMapper, Singleton, Swagger, Repository patterns, etc.
- Architecture Layered MVC and Design DDD (Domain Driven Design)

## .Net Web Developer TimeSolution SRL

#### January 2020 - June 2021.

- My tasks were about the development and maintenance of the main e-commerce system. I also worked with the adaptation of the system for clients from different areas, such as esthetics and veterinaries. Web and Desktop applications with ASP .NET in Web Forms and Web Api projects. Databases developments with SQL Server. Database interaction with ADO .NET and Entity Framework. Front-End development using jQuery, JavaScript, Html and CSS. Back-End development using C#. Version's control with GitHub using Sourcetree interface.
- We used ticket with the clients to solve the bugs or problems with the projects.
- In each project we managed roles, users, custom forms, schedule controls, email and SMS notifications, among other features.

# Full Stack Web Developer Net Core, Angular Grape Software SRL July 2019 – November 2019

 My tasks were about the development and maintenance some government's projects. Databases developments with SQL Server. Database interaction with ADO .NET and Entity Framework and Code First. Front-End development using Angular 8. Back-End development using .Net Core Web Api. Version control with GitHub and task management with Azure Devops. We used Scrum Methodology.

#### **IDIOM**

-. English = I'm studying English in institute Go Idiomas, my current level is B1, and I keep raising my level.

## System support MicroGestion Software August 2017 – June 2019

- This was my first IT job. My tasks were about the development and maintenance of the IBM tool that was Datacap and check the data was correct for electronic invoicing. I worked on site in the clients.
- I used Sql Server 2018 as Database.
- I taught the client how to use the tool.
- Documentation of tool procedures.
- I participated in web development with Java Sprint and Angular 7.
- I used VBScript with the tool to get information from a REST API.

## Operator and administrative M. DODERO Diciembre 2014 – agosto 2018

#### Desempeño:

**Operator**: Pickeo, remission and invoicing of the merchandise, use of Bejerman and SAP system, and remission of orders dispatch of merchandise.

- **Administrative**: covering vacations. Tasks: Stock control, routing, billing, merchandise dispatch, control of orders, closing of the day.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### UTP (UNIVERSITY TECHNICIAN IN PROGRAMMING)

2016 - 2020

#### **BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN ECONOMICS 2012**

Institute Media N3 - Don Torcuato (Tigre)

#### OTHERS.

Institute Educación IT (with valid certificates)

- -. Java para no programadores (04/2016 05/2016)
- -. Introducción a paradigma de objetos (05/2016 06/2016)
- -. Introducción a base de datos y SQL (06/2016 06/2016)
- -. Java standard Programming, J2SE 8.0 (07/2016 09/2016)
- -. Java Web: Servlet, Jsp, JSTL, Struts y AJAX (08/2016 10/2016)
  - -. Redes (05/2015 08/2015)

-. GitHub

.- Aprende a invertir en la Bolsa (11/2019)